<resources>
    <string name="app_name">eMedQue</string>
    <string name="lorem"> MBBS – Thoothukudi Govt Medical college,\n
Distinctions in : Anatomy, Pharmacology, Obstetrics and Gynecology\n
Indian Council of Medical Research(ICMR), Short Term Studentship (STS) award for his Research work in
Microbiology, During II year MBBS\n
Well known for his MBBS question bank (Leonatez) During his MBBS\n
        \n
MD (Paediatrics) – King George Medical University, Lucknow.\n
Divisional level IAP Quiz winner\n
Best Post Graduate Thesis Award by Indian Journal of Pediatrics.\n
Gold Medalist in MD Paediatrics.\n
Publications in National and international level journals\n
Currently working as a consultant Paediatrician In Kauvery Hospital, Trichy\n
Area of interest is Paediatric Emergency and Critical care.</string>

    <string name="about_author">
        \t\t\t Dr.P.Meganathan founder of this app, has a distinguished academic career. He started his
Medical career in Thoothukudi Govt Medical college, Tamil Nadu. He excelled in his career
right from his initial days. He scored distinction in Anatomy, Pharmacology and Obstetrics &amp;
Gynecology. He got the Short Term Studentship award from ICMR(Indian Council Medical
Research) for his excellent research work in Microbiology during his second year under
graduation.  He pursued his post graduation (MD Paediatrics) in prestigious KGMU (King
Geroge’s Medical University), Lucknow. He excelled during his post graduation and acquired
“Gold Medal” for his outstanding performance. He has got the “Best Post Graduate Thesis
Award” from Indian Journal of Pediatrics. He has publications in national and international
journals. Currently he is working as Consultant Paediatrician in Kauvery hospital, Trichy. His
prime interest is on Paediatric critical care and eMedicine. He was well known by various
medical students for his exemplary compilation of university questions, which was useful for
many. Encouragement of many undergraduates made him to start this application.
    </string>

    <string name="about_app">
        \t\t\t UniQue app is developed in especial favour of medical students to aid them in their
university theory exam preparation. This is the first app of this kind for assisting students
who undergo an extremely tense situation during exam preparation. It is invariably a tradition
of every medical college student to cumulate the previous years’ questions for a better and an
organised study schedule.\n\n
How do these questions help? Medical science is vast, extensive and boundless. Every
student should have a detailed reading of the suggested book for a genuine understanding of
the specific subject. However, when the qualifying exams are nearing, these questions help
them to carefully revise the most crucial topics often repeated.\n\n
In this app, one can undoubtedly find last 29 years collection of university questions from
1990 to 2018. All subject questions are properly sorted into chapter-wise and also one can
know how many times each question was repeated. The users enjoy the freedom to sort and
filter the questions as per their need.\n\n
There is, in addition, a specially planned performance desk for the students to assess their
progress individually by graphical representation.\n\n
This specific app is now launched for Tamilnadu Dr.M.G.R.Medical University MBBS
Questions (First Year, Second Year, Prefinal Year &amp; Final Year). We are meticulously
working to revise the app in the upcoming months with questions from Kerala University of
Health Sciences, NTR University of Health Sciences (Andhra Pradesh), Rajiv Gandhi
University of Health Sciences (Karnataka) and other Universities. There will be furthermore
an update of subjectwise images of spotters and OSCE to aid the students for University
practical examination.\n\n
The app will be improvised in future also in the interest of postgraduate students and students
preparing for DNB.\n\n
Please share this app with your friends and fellow colleagues so that everyone can attain its
maximum benefit. Kindly encourage us in ameliorating our work by giving your valuable
feedback and appropriate suggestions.
    </string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="btn_sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="err_msg_name">Enter your full name</string>
    <string name="err_msg_email">Enter valid email address</string>
    <string name="err_msg_password">Enter the password</string>


    <!--1. Dr. P.Meganathan., MBBS., MD (Paed). Editor in Chief-->
    <!--2. Dr. L.Ramya Meganathan MBBS. Co-Editor-->
    <!--Subjects Contributors-->
    <!--3. Dr. S.Anton Remith Riche MBBS., DCH., DNB.,-->
    <!--4. Dr. S.Aravind MBBS., MD (GM)-->
    <!--5. Dr. P.T.Lakshmipriya, MBBS.,-->
    <!--6. Dr. S.Meenoo MBBS., MS(OG)., DNB (OG).,-->
    <!--7. Dr. M.H.Mohamed Muzzammil., MBBS., MD (Paed)-->
    <!--8. Dr. J.Princy Felicia., MBBS., MD (SPM)-->
    <!--9. Dr. A.Ramanathan.,MBBS.,-->
    <!--10. Dr. P.Sivakaran,MBBS.,MS(ORTHO)-->
    <!--11. Dr. J.Vasanth Kumar., MBBS.,-->
    <!--12. Dr. S.P.Vinoth Kumar., MBBS., MD (Paed)-->
    <string name="dr1">Dr. P.Meganathan., MBBS., MD (Paed). Editor in Chief</string>
    <string name="dr2">Dr. L.Ramya Meganathan MBBS. Co-Editor Subjects Contributors</string>
        <string name="dr3">Dr. S.Anton Remith Riche MBBS., DCH., DNB.,</string>
        <string name="dr4">Dr. S.Aravind MBBS., MD (GM)</string>
        <string name="dr5">Dr. P.T.Lakshmipriya, MBBS.,</string>
        <string name="dr6">Dr. S.Meenoo MBBS., MS(OG)., DNB (OG).,</string>
        <string name="dr7">Dr. M.H.Mohamed Muzzammil., MBBS., MD (Paed)</string>
        <string name="dr8">Dr. J.Princy Felicia., MBBS., MD (SPM)</string>
        <string name="dr9">Dr. A.Ramanathan.,MBBS.,</string>
        <string name="dr10">Dr. P.Sivakaran,MBBS.,MS(ORTHO)</string>
        <string name="dr11">Dr. J.Vasanth Kumar., MBBS.,</string>
        <string name="dr12">Dr. S.P.Vinoth Kumar., MBBS., MD (Paed)</string>
    </resources>
